Hawaii Five-O
지난 이야기
파이브 오 팀이
성과가 있네요.
Looks like your Five-O
task force is making an impact.
로라!
Laura!
로라는 제 아버지 증거들을
보내온게 자기였단걸 감췄어요
Laura did not want anybody
to know that she was
sending me evidence
from my father's toolbox.
어떻게 떠난다고 말을 하지?
당신 아이 가진것도..
How do I tell Stan
that I'm leaving, and that
I'm pregnant
with your child?
저 여잘 봤어요
That's the woman I saw.
맞네요
5번 이에요
That's her. Number five.
주지사가 뭔가
숨기고 있는것 같아
I think the governor's
hiding something.
설마 주지사 관저에
침입한건 아니겠지?
Tell me you didn't break
into the governor's house.
당신이 무슨 짓 했는지 알아!
I know what you did!
모두 제가 관리하고 있습니다
I have everything under control.
스티브 맥개럿
당신을 체포합니다
Steve McGarrett,
you are under arrest.
- 놔줘
- 놔줄 수 없어
- Let him go.
- I can't let him go.
할 수 있잖아
우리 관할이야
Yes, you can. We have
jurisdiction. We are Five-O.
잘 이해가 안가나 본데
파이브 오는 이제 끝났어
You don't understand.
There is no Five-O anymore.
DCinside 기타미드갤러리
나엘남캐
美 태평양 국립 묘지
- 7일 후 -
나엘남캐 한글자막/싱크수정
수정금지/자유배포
하와이 주 교도소
- 오아후 -
맥개럿!
McGarrett.
면회왔다
You have a visitor.
Why are you smiling at me?
웃음이 나와?
넥타이 안 했네
잘 어울려
You're not wearing
a tie, it suits you.
그래, 안 매고 있어
No, I'm not wearing a tie.
짤린 경찰한테 맞는
드레스 코드는 없으니까
'Cause there's no dress code
for an out-of-work cop.
우 펫 정보는 없어?
You get any leads on Wo Fat?
Uh, no. Nothing yet.
응, 아직까진 없어
가족은 어때?
레이첼은 뭐하고
How's your family?
How's Rachel?
아직 입덧은 안 하지?
She getting morning
sickness yet?
응, 뭐 괜찮은 것 같아
Yeah, she's, uh...
She's excellent.
있잖아, 네가 외지인
안 좋아하는건 아는데
Listen, I know you
don't like visitors,
이 분이 막무가내라..
but this guy wouldn't
take no for an answer, so...
맞춰보자
주지사가 자초한 일이지?
Let me guess,
the governor had it coming?
여기까지
안 오셔도 됬습니다
You, uh, you didn't have
to come down here, sir.
자네 괜찮나?
You okay, son?
그렇습니다
I'm fine.
훈련 받은대로 입니다
Nothing Hell Week
didn't train me for.
부지사가 자네 재판
앞 당기려 한다던데?
Your man tells me
the lieutenant governor's
trying to move up your trial.
새로온 사람이 시민들에게
자긴 관용이 없단걸
I heard. The new guy, he
wants to show the public
he's a zero tolerance
type, so convicting me
보이려고 주지사 살인건을
첫 직무로 정했다더군요
of Governor Jameson's murder
is his first order of business.
그렇게 되지 않도록
하는게 우리 일 이겠지
Well, we are here to make
sure that doesn't happen.
어딜가시려고?
Where do you think
you're going?
뭐 문제라도 있습니까?
Is there something
I can help you with?
네가 한 짓인거 알아
We know it was you.
맥개럿이랑 네가 자리를
바꾸는건 시간문제야
It's just a matter of time
before you're trading places
with McGarrett.
진급 축하합니다
캘리 경위님
Congratulations on the
promotion, Lieutenant Kelly.
영리하시군요
경찰에 복직하신걸 보니
Smart move, rejoining HPD.
한 시간 준다
You got one hour.
내 동생 죽었지?
My brother's dead, isn't he?
그럼 네 아버지도 죽어야 돼
Then so's your father.
안 돼!
No!
안녕, 스티브
Hello, Steve.
내 말 아주 잘 들어..
Now listen to me
very carefully, Steve...
재소자, 물러서
Prisoner, step back!
물러서!
Step back!
알았지 스티브?
You hear me, Steve?
알아 들었어!?
You hear me?!
(Hawaii Five-O
theme song plays)
Hawaii Five-O 2x01
Ha'i'ole (Unbreakable)
Original Air Date on September 19, 2011
♪ Hawaii Five-O 2x01 ♪
Ha'i'ole
Original Air Date on September 19, 2011
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
나엘남캐 제공
파이브 오 본부
이봐요
Hey.
봉쇄 테이프 끊어
먹었으니 경위님이
You should have to
arrest yourself for
- 체포되야 되는거 아닙니까?
- 괜찮아
- breaking that seal, Lieutenant.
- It's okay.
하나 더 들고왔어
I brought a spare.
자네가 친호 캘리 맞나?
You're Chin Ho Kelly, right?
맥개럿이 아주 칭찬하던데
John McGarrett
spoke highly of you.
조 화이트네
Joe White.
- 맥개럿은 어떻게 아시죠?
- 같이 복무했었네
- How do you know John?
- We served together.
맥개럿은 내가 기억 하는것보다
더 많이 날 살려줬었지
He saved my ass more times
than I'd like to remember.
보답을 하러 왔네
I'm here to
return the favor.
그래서 어쩐 일이야?
일주일이나 날
So. What's up, buddy?
You've been ducking me
- 피해 다녔잖아
- 약간 바빴었어
for about a week now.
- I've been a little busy.
친구들 더 잡아 넣으려
바빴던건 아니겠지?
You've been busy?
What are you doing,
putting more of your friends
behind bars?
나라고 방법이
있엇을것 같아?
So you think I had a choice?
- 그치
- 맥개럿은 주지사 관저에서
Mm-hmm.
McGarrett was standing over
시체옆에 총을 들고 있었어
the governor's body with
a gun in his hand, Danny.
뒤에 있던 SWAT팀 전부가
내가 본 걸 똑같이 봤었고
I had a full SWAT team
right behind me, who saw
exactly the same things.
그 상황에서
내가 뭘 어떻게 해?
Now, what was I
supposed to do?
좋은 질문이야
That's a good question.
I'm glad you asked.
네가 했어야 될 일은 우리가
수사 하게 만드는 거였어
Because what I think
that you should have done
is let Five-O investigate,
우릴 해체시키고 떠나서
경찰에 복직하는 대신에
instead of dismantling it.
Instead of running off
and joining HPD.
- 떠나갔다?
- 그래
- Running off?
- Yeah.
민간인으로 보단 경찰신분으로
더 잘 도울 수 있다 생각했어
I knew that I could help
McGarrett more as a cop
than as an unemployed civilian.
아직 안 끝났나?
Are you two done?
지금 하는 대화는 아무
도움도 안되는 것 같네만
Because I'm fairly certain
that this conversation
isn't helping Steve one bit.
I saw Wo Fat at the
funeral this morning.
오늘 장례식에서
우 팻을 봤어
Hold on. You saw...
Why didn't you arrest him?
왜 체포 안 했는데?
With what?
We got nothing.
뭘 가지고?
증거가 없잖아
탄도검사에 따르면 맥개럿이
들고있던 총이 살인도구 였어
Ballistics confirmed the gun
that McGarrett had in his hand
was the murder weapon.
발사 된 직후
맥개럿 손에 쥐어졌으니
And since it was
freshly discharged
when Wo Fat put
it into his hand,
맥개럿 옷에서
탄흔도 발견됬지
lab found traces of GSR
on McGarrett's clothing.
맥개럿이 쏘지 않았단걸
증명해야 해
The key is gonna be proving
that he didn't fire it.
Okay. Hold on.
잠깐만
CCTV는 어때?
What about the security cameras?
꺼져있었어
No, they were down.
스티브가 다
망가뜨려 놨어
Steve disabled them all
during his break-in.
진짜 범인이 오고
가는건 안 찍힌건가?
So you got no footage of the
real killer coming or going?
네
No.
좋았어
All right.
전기충격기 때문에 목에
자국이 있잖아, 그건 어때?
Steve got blasted in the neck
with a stun gun.
He got marks on his neck.
What about that?
검찰 쪽에선
그 부분을 제외 할거야
Prosecuting attorney will
have that tossed out.
McGarrett took out
the governor's
맥개럿이 경호인력들을
쓰러뜨리는 과정에서
entire security detail.
They can easily make the case
아무런 상처도
안 생겼다 보긴 힘들대
that any physical
trauma occurred then.
우리가 할 일이 많을것 같군
Sounds like we got a lot
of work ahead of us.
이 우 팻이란 작자
신상은 확보하고 있나?
Do you guys have a dossier
on this Wo Fat character?
제나 카예가 가지고 있어요
CIA에서 일 했엇어요
Jenna Kaye does.
She used to work for the CIA.
그럼 정중하게 부탁해야 겠군
Well, I'll try not to
hold that against her.
어디가면 만날 수 있지?
Where can I find her?
마할로 모텔
17번방이요
Mahalo Inn. Room 17.
어딘지 알아
부탁좀 하지
I know the place.
Do me a favor.
내가 만나러 간다고
전화 좀 해줘
Give her a ring, tell
her I'm on my way.
스티브를 훈련시키셨대
He, uh, he trained Steve.
Oh.
그래서 책임이 있단건가?
So it's his fault?
코노랑 얘기 해봤는데
정직 때문에 많이 힘든가봐
I spoke to Kono,
and she's not taking
her suspension very well.
Yeah.
내사과에선 계속
수사를 진행하려 해
IA's not backing off.
The investigation's
still ongoing.
코노의 뱃지를
원하는거라고
They want her badge, Danny.
너 마치 빛 한 줄기 같아
다시 만나 반갑다
You, my friend,
are a ray of sunshine today.
It's really good to see you.
그래
Yeah.
윌리엄입니다
Williams.
언제?
When?
알았어
Okay.
가만히 있어
내가 갈게
Don't move. I'm on my way.
이게 네 계획이었냐?
What, this was
your plan all along?
맥개럿한테 죄를 씌워서
여기서 죽이려고?
Huh? Frame McGarrett, get him in
here so you could take him out?
난 죽이려 한게 아니야
목숨을 구해주려 한거지
I wasn't trying to kill him.
I was trying to save his life.
목..목숨을 구해준다고?
T-trying to save his life?
내가 걔를 쑤시고 싶었으면
이미 쑤시고도 남았어
Believe me,
if I wanted to gut the man,
I would've done it.
대신 낮은 복부를 찔렀지
I stabbed him in the abdomen,
low and to the center,
- 중요 장기들을 피하려고
- 왜 그랬는데?
avoiding all the vital organs.
- Why would you do that?
그건..
Because...
탈출 할 수 있는
기회를 주려고 한거야
that would give him
the best chance to escape.
탈출?
Escape?
탈출이라니 무슨 소리야?
What the hell you
talking about, escape?
What do you mean?
우 팻이 나한테 자길
죽이라고 명령한걸 말해줬다
I told McGarrett that Wo Fat
ordered me to kill him.
If Wo Fat wanted
to kill McGarrett,
맥개럿을 죽이고 싶었으면
왜 주지사 죽일 때 안 죽였지?
why didn't he just do it
when he killed the governor?
You're the detective,
I'm sure you can figure it out.
형사는 그 쪽이잖아
충분히 알 수 있을텐데?
주지사를 제거하고 싶어서
맥개럿한테 혐의를 씌우고
He needed the governor
out of the way
so he pinned her murder
on McGarrett.
맥개럿이
감옥에서 죽게되면
And when McGarrett's killed
in prison by the man
누구도 의심하지
않을거란 생각이지
he put away, no one asks
any questions. Is that it?
이해가 빠르군
You two catch on fast.
명령을 따르지
않은 이유는 뭐지?
Still doesn't explain
why you didn't follow orders.
내가 차가운 나쁜놈일진
몰라도, 바보는 아니야
I may be a soulless bastard,
Detective, but I'm no fool.
우 팻은 마지막으로
거래를 한 뒤 사라질거다
Wo Fat is making one last deal,
and then he's going
to disappear.
신발끈이 헐렁한 상태로
떠나진 않을거라고
He's not going to do that
without tying up loose ends.
그 신발끈이 너고?
And by loose ends,
you mean you, right?
Unless McGarrett
kills him first.
맥개럿이 우 팻을 먼저
죽여버리면 아니지
스티브 소식은 없어
하와이 경찰 전 병력이 배치됬고
Still no sign of Steve,
but HPD's out in full force.
나더러 현장에서
추적을 도우라더군
They want to deploy me
in the field to help coordinate.
나 잠깐 집에서 할 일이 있어
Okay, listen. I need to set
up shop here, at my place.
나 왔어
Hey.
- 너 여기서 뭐해?
- 맥개럿 소식 들었어
- What are you doing here?
- Heard about McGarrett.
대체 뭔 생각이래요?
What does he think he's doing?
우 팻을 쫒고 있대
He's going after Wo Fat.
그럼 도와줘야죠
Okay. So we have to help him.
우 팻이 누군지 생각해보면
조금 어려울것 같다
Yeah, that's gonna be
a little difficult,
considering who
we're dealing with.
스티브는 우리랑
연락도 안 할거고
Okay, Steve will
not contact us.
우리까지 잡혀가는걸
원하지 않을거야
He won't want us implicated
for aiding and abetting.
그럼 우 팻을
먼저 찾아보죠
Okay. So we have
to find Wo Fat first.
윌 링은 어디있는지
알고 있을거야
Will Ling might know
where he is.
- 윌 링? 걔가 누군데?
- 우 팻 똘마니야
- Will Ling? Who's Will Ling?
- One of Wo Fat's lapdogs
묘지에서 자기 지갑을
잊어버린 사람이기도 하지
who happened to, uh, drop
his wallet at the cemetery.
좋았어
Nice.
이 놈을 따라가면
두목도 찾을 수 있겠지
If we follow this guy, he's
bound to lead us to his boss.
내가 신원조회랑
전화추적하고 수배 내릴게
I can run his ID, trace his
cell, run surveillance.
네가 어떻게 하게?
How are you gonna do that?
넌 DB 접속할
권한도 없잖아
You don't have access
to HPD's database.
오빠 비밀번호 쓸거야
I'll use your password.
- 좋은 생각은 아니네
- 뭐가?
- Oh! That's not a good idea.
- What?
넌 지금 뱃지가 없잖아
경찰이 지원해줄지 잘 몰라
You're not carrying
a badge anymore, Kono.
I can't guarantee HPD back up.
오빠들이
날 지원해 주잖아
You guys are my back up.
너도 참 맥개럿이랑
너무 오래 어울렸네
Definitely been hanging out
with McGarrett too long now.
그래서 계획이
있어요 없어요?
Okay, so do we have a plan
or what?
계획은 있지
Yes, we have a plan.
너가 링을 쫓아가서
뭐라도 나오면 알려줘
You go after Ling-- let us know
if you find anything.
우린 경찰에서 찾기전에
먼저 맥개럿을 찾아야 하니까
In the meantime,
we need to find McGarrett
before HPD does, okay?
♪ ♪
항저우에서 차량 폭파가
그 놈 작품이었소?
The car bomb in Hangzhou,
that was him?
들어 보셨나봐요
You heard of it?
그렇다고 할 수 있지
Yeah, you could
say that.
우 팻 이란놈은
손을 더럽히기 좋아하는군
This Wo Fat likes to
get his hands dirty.
Hmm.
정체를 밝혀내니 자기 방어에
적극적으로 나서더군요
Now that we've exposed him,
he's taken a more active role
in his own self-preservation.
자료가 완벽하네
This is very thorough.
잘 아는 사이인가 봐
You seem to know him
pretty well.
개인적인 사정이 좀 있죠
This one was personal to me.
대니 전화에요
It's Danny.
여보세요
Hey.
뭐라고요?
What happened?
바로 전할게요
Yeah, I'll tell him
right now.
맥개럿이 탈옥했대요
McGarrett escaped from prison.
인내심이 좋은 편은 아니었지
Patience was never
his strong suit.
가봐야겠어요
저희 도움이 필요할 거에요
Well, we should
get going.
They're gonna
need our help.
이것들 다 맥개럿 물건이었나?
These things belonged
to John McGarrett, right?
네, 근데요?
Yeah. What does
that matter?
잘 모르겠네..
I don't know.
상관 없으면
내가 가져가지
I'm gonna take this,
if you don't mind.
그러세요..
어디 가시는데요?
Sure. Where are you going?
- 맥개럿을 도와야죠
- 괜찮을거야
McGarrett needs our help.
He'll be fine.
괜찮을거라니
무슨 말이에요?
What do you mean,
he'll be fine?
- 어떻게 확신해요?
- 내가 훈련시켰다네
How do you know?
I trained him.
맥스 버그만의 집
- 칼리히 -
911입니다
어떻게 도와드립니까?
911. What is your emergency?
맥개럿 소령?
Commander McGarrett?
맥개럿 소령
내 말 들려요?
Commander McGarrett,
can you hear me?
치료까지 해줬는데
스티브라고 부르셔야죠
Max, least you can do
after patching me up
is call me Steve.
아, 고마워요
Oh. Well, thank you...
스티브
Steve.
집에 강제로 들어와서 미안해요
I'm sorry I broke in
your house.
제가 좀.
I, um...
정말 갈데가 없었거든요
I didn't really have
anywhere else to go.
사과는 안 해도 되요
No apology is necessary.
사실, 집에 찾아올 정도로
우리가 친했다니 기쁜데요
In fact, I'm quite humbled
that you feel comfortable
enough to come to me.
그래도 그 부상은 어디서
얻으셨는지는 궁금해요
However, I am curious as to how
you acquired that wound.
제가 봤을때
그건 조잡하게
I'm guessing
that it was
깎이고 소독 안 된
금속 조각인 것 같은데요
a crudely sharpened piece
of unsterilized metal...
감옥에서 찔린거에요
I got shanked in prison, Max.
아.
Oh.
그렇다면
So then...
적법한 방법으로
여기 오신건 아니군요?
you didn't come by that uniform
in a legal manner?
뉴스 안 보시죠?
You don't watch the news,
do you?
안 보려고 해요
I try not to.
되게 무섭거든요
It's very scary.
제 룸메이트는
본토에 가족을 보러 갔어요
My roommate is visiting
family on the mainland.
둘이 사이즈가
비슷할 것 같네요
You two are approximately
the same size.
고마워요
Thanks, buddy.
누구에요?
Who is it?
- 괜찮아요
- 문 열지마요
It's all right.
Max, don't get the door.
괜찮다니까요!
It's all right.
문 열지 마요!
Max, don't answer the door!
대체 넌..
What the hell is
뭐가 문제야?
응? 뭐냐고?
the matter with you, huh?
What is the matter with you?!
탈옥을 하고
경찰관을 공격해?!
Breaking outta jail,
taking out a cop?!
너 정말 미쳤냐?
Have you lost
your mind?
왜 자꾸 소리질러?
Why are you yelling at me?
- 소리 안 질렀어!
- 소리 지르셨어요
- I'm not yelling at you!
- Actually, you were
아주 시끄러운 방법으로
의사표현을 하셨죠
expressing yourself
in a very loud manner.
아저씬 다물어요
너 미쳤지?
Hey, zip it, Kermit, okay?
Have you lost your mind?
- 다른 방법이 없잖아
- 다른 방법이라고?
- What choice did I have, Danny?
- What choice did you have?
저건 또 무슨 말 이야?
- Shh, shh! Shh, shh.
- What does that even mean?!
너 괜찮지?
You all right?
물어봐줘서 고마워, 형
나 괜찮단다!
Thank you for asking, Chin.
Yeah, I'm all right!
- 맥스 덕 분이야
- 전화해줘서 감사해요
- Thanks to Max.
- Mahalo for calling.
오면서 따라온 사람 없어?
Anybody follow you guys?
잠복수사팀에서 따라 왔는데
우리가 따돌렸어
Undercover unit tried to, but
we managed to shake the tail.
순찰차 훔쳤다며?
어디다 버리고 왔어?
Hey, heard you stole a squad
car-- where'd you ditch it?
여기서 조금 남쪽에
공사현장 뒤에 놨어
A few blocks south.
It's behind a construction site.
내가 노스 쇼어에 갖다
놓으면 경찰이 햇갈릴거야
I'll take it up
to the North Shore,
distract HPD.
형도 경찰이야
잊었어?
You are HPD, Chin. You remember?
뱃지에 그렇게 써있다 해도
나도 파이브 오야
Hey, just 'cause
the badge says HPD,
doesn't mean I'm not Five-O.
너도 알잖아
You know that.
형은 할 일 한거야
You did what you had
to do, okay?
지금은 우 팻을 찾아야 해
알겠지?
Right now, I want to find
Wo Fat. You understand?
코노가 조직원
한 명 쫒고 있어
Kono's following one
of his guys right now.
우 팻이 나타난다면
바로 출발 할 거야
As soon as we get eyes on him,
we'll be there.
여보세요
네, 여기 있어요
Hello. Yeah, he's right here
스피커폰으로 돌릴게요
I'll put you on speakerphone.
스티브, 괜찮나?
Steve, you okay?
그렇습니다
Yes, sir.
어디십니까?
Where are you?
네가 얘기 해봐야 될
사람을 찾았어
I found someone
you need to talk to.
푸우키나 가 5423.
5423 Puuikena Drive.
기다리고 있겠네
I'll be waiting out front.
알겠습니다
지금 출발합니다
Copy that. I'm on my way.
잠깐, 출발을 한다니?
Whoa-whoa. What do you mean,
you're on your way?
너 어디도 못가잖아
You're not on your way anywhere.
지금 넌 탈옥수야
기억 안 나?
You're a fugitive,
you remember that?
너도 들었잖아
뭔가 찾으셨어
You heard the man.
He's got something.
나도 들었지
안 들은 사람 없어
Yeah, I heard him.
We all heard him.
뭘 찾은게 아니지
주소 하나가 딸랑이라고!
He doesn't have anything.
He's got an address, that's all!
아니면 요다 장로께서
너한테만 텔레파시를 보낸거야?
Unless Master Yoda can send
telepathic messages
that the rest of us
cannot hear...
사실 요다는
텔레파시 능력이 없어요
Actually, Yoda technically
didn't have telepathic powers.
진짜로?
지금 그럴거에요?
Seriously?
Right now?
제발 좀, 제발 들어봐
Please. Please listen to me.
우리 좀 논의를
해봐야 되지 않을까?
Is there any way that I can
talk you out of this?
- 언젠 그 방법이 통했어?
- 안 통했지
- Has it ever worked before, Danny?
- No.
- 그러니까, 좀 가자고
- 알았어
- Okay, so let's go, yeah?
- Okay.
기다려
Wait-wait-wait.
너네 차 끌고 나갈 수 없어
경찰쪽에서 감시 할 거니까
You guys can't take your car.
HPD's gonna be on
the look out for it.
제가 도울 수 있겠네요
Then perhaps I can help.
그래, 그게 맞아
Yes, you are. Yes, you...
넌 100% 물방울 무늬 옷
입은 원숭이야
100%, you are a monkey
in a polka dot dress.
아빠가 너무 사랑해
다시 보게 되서 너무 행복해
And I love you and I'm very
happy that I will see you
이틀 후면 오잖아?
그렇지
in a couple days, okay?
That's right.
대노가 사랑한다
Danno loves you.
알았어, 우리 아가
All right, babe. All right.
내가 틀릴 수도 있는데
You know, I could be wrong,
it's rare,
너 별로 안 행복해보여
but you don't look happy.
속에서는 행복하고 있어
Well, I am happy
on the inside.
You're a bad liar.
거짓말 되게 못하네
What are you doing?
Get down.
You're supposed to be
뭐해? 어서 숙여
너 투명인간이잖아
좀 숙여줄래?
the invisible man.
Would you get down?
- 와 주제를 바꿀려 그래?
- 주제 바꾼적 없거든?
- Why are you changing the subject?
- I'm not changing the subject.
너 주제 바꾸고 있잖아
무슨 일 인데?
You are changing the subject,
Danny. What's going on?
레이첼이 다시
하와이로 와, 됬어?
Put your head down! Rachel is
moving back to Hawaii, okay?
저지에서 살고 있다며?
You told me
she was staying in Jersey.
왜 다시 오는건데?
Why she moving back to Hawaii?
그니까
She's, uh,
스탠 때문에
다시 오는거야
she's moving back in
with Stan.
아이고
Oh, man.
뱃속 애기 아빠가
그 사람이야?
The baby's his?
생각했던것 보다
임신이 더 빨랐나봐
Turns out she's further along
than she thought.
그러니 애를 위해서
스탠이랑 노력할거래
And so she's gonna try
to make it work with Stan
for the, for the kid's sake.
좀 숙여 줄래?
제발 좀 숙여
Would you get down, please?
Would you please get down?
미안해, 대니
I'm sorry, Danny.
괜찮아
I'm fine.
처음에 잘 안됬으니
It didn't work out
the first time,
두 번이라고 뭐가 다르겠어?
so who's to this time would be
any different, right?
그렇게 보진 말아줘
Please don't look at me
like that.
나 괜찮다고 했잖아
그렇게 쳐다보진 마
I said I'm fine. I'm asking you
not to give me that look, okay?
나 운전에 집중해야 돼
I'm more worried
about my car, okay?
제가 여기서 부터 맡죠
Okay, I'll take it
from here.
한참 즐기고 있었는데..
Actually, I'm enjoying myself
very much.
이런 멋진녀석 이라면
선사시대 화석 수집품인
I may even cash in
my prehistoric fossil collection
제 자동차도 싸게 현금으로
넘길 의향도 있어요
to put a down payment on one
of these bad boys.
나와요
Come on.
게다가, 전 운전 안 하면
차 멀미 한답니다
Also, if I don't drive,
I get carsick.
잡히지만 마요
Just don't get pulled over.
찾은거 있어?
Hey, what ya got?
그 똘마니 찾았어
Hey, I got your lapdog.
아직까지
우 팻은 안 보여
But so far, no sign of Wo Fat.
이 하울리 아저씨는 누구지?
Wait. Who's this haole?
우 팻 조직원 처럼은
안 보이는데..
He doesn't look like
one of Wo Fat's crew.
우 팻이 하려는 거래랑
관련있는 사람 일거야
He could be part of the deal
Wo Fat's trying
to pull off.
알았어, 사진 찍어서
안면인식 돌려볼게
All right, I'll get a picture
and run it through
facial recognition.
뭐 뜨면 전화해
Call me when you get a hit.
이거 알아 보겠어?
Recognize this?
네, 제 아버지
공구상자에 있던거에요
Yeah, it was in
my father's toolbox.
이건 히데키 모코토라는
사람 물건이었어
It belonged to a man named
Hideki Mokoto,
전직 일본 조종사였지
former Japanese pilot.
그는 진주만 폭격으로
훈장을 수여 받았다
He earned that medal
for bombing Pearl Harbor.
- 그 후, 네 아버지에게 줬고
- 왜 준거에요?
- He gave it to your father.
- Why?
너한테 직접
얘기하고 싶어해
He wants to tell you that
himself.
잠시만요
아직 살아 있는거에요?
Wait a minute,
this guy's still alive?
가보거라
Through that door.
네 아비 눈을 닮았어
You have his eyes.
정리 좀 해볼게요
Let me just get this straight.
진주만 폭격 이후에
갑자기 부자가 되선
After Pearl Harbor,
this guy strikes it rich,
여기에 정착할 생각을 한 뒤
이 섬을 날려 버리려 해요?
very rich, obviously,
and he decides
to move here and dedicate his
life to cleaning up this island?
- 개인적인 속죄라고 하더군
- 아.
- He called it a personal atonement.
- Aha.
맥개럿네 아버지는
어떻게 꾀어낸거죠?
And how does McGarrett's
father come into play?
아리조나에
추모식에서 만났다더군
They met at a memorial service
for the Arizona
스티브 할아버지가
거기서 돌아가셨거든
where Steve's grandfather died.
And it was there
모코토가 그 때
용서를 구하려고 했었지
that Mokoto approached John
and asked for his forgiveness.
결국에 둘은
서로 친구가 되었어
Ultimately the two
of them became friends.
몇년 뒤 모코토가
그를 고용했어
A couple years later
Mokoto hired him.
경찰당국과 지역정치계의
부폐 때문에 화가 나서 말이야
He'd gotten upset
over corruption in
the police department
and local politics.
그래서 존에게
비밀 수사를 부탁했지
So he asked John
to secretly conduct
an investigation.
그 때 주지사가 우 팻과
동침을 하고 있단걸 알았군요
Okay, and that's when
John finds out
that the governor's in bed
with Wo Fat.
그래
Yeah.
존은 죽기전에 모코토에게
관계를 밝힐 증거가 있다고 했지
And before he died,
John told Mokoto
that he had the evidence
어떤 증거요?
that would prove it.
- What evidence?
모코토도 잘 몰라
Mokoto didn't know.
존은 그걸 몰로카이에
숨겼다고만 말했거든
All John said was
that he hid it on Molokai.
왜 제게 말을
안 하셨을까요?
Why didn't he tell me?
네 아버지가 한 일은
Everything your father did
가족을 보호하기 위해서 였다
was to protect his family.
코올리나 선착장
- 카폴레이 -
찾았다
Gotcha.
차 안에서
이걸 찾았습니다
We found this
in her car.
칼라코와 양
말 해보시죠
Tell me, Ms. Kalakaua,
여기서 뭐하고 계십니까?
what are you doing here?
공식적인 수사가 아닐텐데요
정직 당하셨으니까요
It can't be official business,
you're suspended.
내가 누군지 아시는군
So you know who I am.
날 겁주려고 한건가?
Is that supposed
to intimidate me?
아니요
No.
이 사람들 할 일이니까요
That's their job.
전 단지 사업가입니다
I'm just a businessman.
커트 허프씨 한테
뭘 파시려고?
So what are you selling
to Kurt Hauff?
일본 속담이 하나 있죠
The Japanese have a saying:
'이와누 가 하나'
(모를 수록 좋다)
Iwanu ga hana.
"꽃은 말하지 않는다"
"Not speaking
is the flower."
좋은 하루 되시죠
Good day, Ms. Kalakaua.
여깄어요
Here you go.
고마워요
Mahalo.
저기 죄송한데
화장실 좀 써도 될까요?
Hi. I was wondering
if I could use your bathroom?
그럼요
Of course.
빙수 먼저 산다면야
You're going to have to buy
a shave ice first.
카마코나, 진심이에요?
Come on, Kamekona, seriously?
뭐 하나 알려줄게
Let me give you a tip.
물 밑 작업들은
진짜처럼 보이게 해야해
The key to undercover work--
you got to make it look real.
체리맛 주세요
I'll have a cherry.
아이스크림?
아니면 팥 올려줘?
With ice cream or adzuki beans?
상관없어요
아무거나 해요
I don't care. You choose.
팥이 딱이지
Beans definitely.
배고파요?
Hey, hungry?
저 위장한거에요
It's part of my cover.
뭔가 건진 것 같아요
I think I have something.
당신 아버지 공구상자에서
나온 락커 열쇠요
It's the locker key
from your father's toolbox.
마코토씨에 따르면
Based on Mokoto's intel,
몰로카이에 있는
공항이에요
I traced it to the airport
on Molokai.
네 아버지가
증거를 숨긴 곳 이구나
That's where your father
hid the evidence.
누가 몰래 카메라
설치 하는것 같은데
Looks like someone set up
a hidden camera.
잠깐만
Wait, wait, wait.
저기 주지사 서재잖아
That's the governor's study.
맞아, 그런 것 같네
Yeah, looks like it.
이 사람 누구야?
Who's this guy?
내 아버지야
That's my father.
이 카메라
아직 거기 있진 않을까?
This camera--
what if it's still there?
만약 있다면
If that's the case,
주지사 살인건이
영상에 남아있을지도 몰라
then the governor's murder
may have been captured on video,
right?
챙 형사입니다
This is Detective Chang.
탈옥수를 찾은것 같습니다
I think I may have found
our fugitive.
주지사 관저
- 호놀룰루 -
카메라가 없으면 맥개럿이랑
감방 같이 써야 될거야
We'd better be right about this,
or we're going to be sharing
a cell with McGarrett.
내가 윗 침대 찜할래
I call top bunk.
카메라가 이 방향으로
가리킨 것 같은데
Looks like the camera was
pointed in this direction.
여기 맞아
딱 이 각도였어
Yeah, this is it.
This is the angle right here.
좋아, 어디보자
Okay, come on.
친
Chin.
저 안에 렌즈가 있나보군
That could be
a lens right there.
당연히 드라이버는
안 가져왔지?
You didn't happen to bring
your screwdriver, did you?
드라이버? 집에 놓고온
망치 옆에 있을텐데
Screw...? I left it at home
with my hammer.
도대체 무슨 일이십니까?
What do you think you're doing?
여긴 주지사 관저인데
This is the governor's
residence.
누구 길래 여기서
뭘 하는거요?
Who are you and what
are you doing here?
데닝 부지사님
Lieutenant Governor Denning,
저는 친 호 경위입니다
uh, I'm
Lieutenant Chin Ho Kelly.
여기는 데니 윌리엄스 형사고요
This is
Detective Danny Williams.
함부로 들어와서
대단히 죄송합니다
We're very sorry
to intrude like this.
잠시만요
윌리엄스? 캘리?
Wait a minute--
Williams... Kelly?
파이브 오 팀인가요?
From Five-O?
이미 해체 된 걸로
알고 있는데?
I thought that was dismantled.
그렇습니다
하지만 저희가 이곳에
Yes, sir, it was.
But we have reason to believe
주지사 살인사건에 관해
that there's a key piece of
evidence here that has to do
아주 중요한 증거가
있다고 생각했습니다
with the governor's murder.
어떤 증거요?
What kind of evidence?
네 등치 큰 친구
대단한 사업가더라
Your big friend out there
is quite the entrepreneur.
새우 트럭 오픈계획을
전부 말해주던데
He's telling me all about his
plans to open a shrimp truck.
오픈 초기부터 함께 할
생각이 있냐고 묻기도 했어
He asked me
if I wanted
to get in on the ground floor.
카메코나는 좋은 친구에요
Kamekona's good people.
주변에 좋은 사람들이 많구나
You got a lot of good people
around you.
넌 좋은 팀을 꾸렸어
You put together a nice team.
자네 괜찮나?
Are you okay, son?
모코토와 얘기한 후 부터
엄청 조용해
You've been
awful quiet
ever since we left Mokoto's.
무슨 생각이야?
What's on your mind?
아버지가 절 보낼 때
전 고작 15살이었어요
I was only 15 years old
when my father sent me away.
널 보호하려고 했던거야
He did that to protect you.
저도 압니다
I know, I know.
그 때 입대를 하고
근무지도 배치 받았죠
But then I joined the service.
All right, I got deployed.
그 후론 아버지랑 시간을
많이 보내지 못 했어요
I didn't get a lot of time
to spend with him
as an adult.
지금에야 아버지에 대해
모르는게 많단걸 느꼈어요
And now I'm realizing
there's all this stuff
about him that I never knew.
아버지가 숨겨둔 비밀들이
절 성가시게 합니다
He had all these secrets,
and it bugs me.
이 일이 끝나면 비밀에 대해
조금은 알 수 있겠지
Well, when this is over,
maybe we can shed some light
on those secrets.
알지 말아야
될 수도 있죠
Maybe we shouldn't.
왜?
Why?
우 팻이 저더러 가족의
과거를 파헤치지 말라더군요
Wo Fat warned me not to dig
into my family's past.
결과가 맘에
안 들수도 있다 했어요
He said I might not
like what I find.
무슨 뜻 일까요?
What did he mean by that?
자네가 아버지를 잘 몰랐어도
아버지가 널 알았잖아
Listen, son, you may not
have known your father,
but he knew you.
코로나도에서
네가 훈련 받을때
When you were
training at Coronado,
나한테 매주 전화를 했어
he called to check
in with me every week
어떻게 하고 있나
궁금해 했지
to see how you were doing.
어렸을 적 얘기를 하자면
And as for when
you were younger,
존도 너 만큼이나
무척 힘들어 했어
well, trust me,
that was as hard on him
as it was on you.
34년 간이나
네 아버질 알았는데
In the 34 years
I knew your father,
I saw him cry twice.
우는 모습을
딱 두 번 봤어
네 어머니 장례식 때랑
널 보낸 날이었지
At your mother's funeral,
and the day he sent you away.
좋은사람 이었다
He was a good man.
다르게 생각해볼
이유도 없어
And there's no reason
to think otherwise.
손님이 왔어
We got company.
스티브 맥개럿
현재 건물을 포위중이다
McGarrett, we have
the building surrounded.
손을 들고
밖으로 나와라
Come out with your hands up.
어떻게 할거야?
What are you going to do?
우리한테 말만 해
Yeah, brah,
just give us the word.
꿇어
Down.
당장 무릎 꿇어!
Down! On your knees now!
무릎 꿇으라고
Get down, McGarrett!
수갑 채워
Lock him up.
범인을 은닉한 죄로
I want those two arrested
- for harboring a fugitive.
- Listen to me--
너희 두 명도 체포한다
저 사람들은
아무 관련 없습니다
they have nothing to do
with this, okay?
제가 도우라고 협박했어요
I forced them to help,
you understand?
저들은 아무 관련이 없어요
They have nothing
to do with this.
이봐요
Hey.
풀어줘요
Let him go.
들었잖습니까
어서 수갑 푸세요
You heard the man,
get the cuffs off him.
- 대체 뭔 일 입니까?
- 진정 해요
What the hell is this about?
Just relax, okay?
엉뚱한 사람을
잡았네, 경관
You have the wrong man,
Detective.
맥개럿은 무죄야
McGarrett's innocent.
주지사를 죽이지 않았으니까
He didn't kill the governor.
적은 내가 아니야, 스티브
I am not the enemy, Steve.
난 내게 신의를 보였던
사람들에겐 항상 신의를 보였어
I have always been loyal
to the people
who are loyal to me.
그게 로라 힐스를
죽인 이유입니까?
Is that why you had
Laura Hills murdered?
신의를 보이지 못해서?
Because she was disloyal?
그래
Yes.
어떻게 하면 좋아?
저 자를 없애야 해
What are we going to do?
We have to get rid of him.
모두 제가 관리하고 있습니다
I have everything under control.
저게 그 놈이 아니라고요?
저게 우 팻이 아니라고요?
You can't even see it's him.
You can't even see it's Wo Fat.
그래, 하지만
확실한 건
No, but what we do clearly see,
자네가 주지사를
죽이지 않았단 거지
is that you didn't kill
the governor.
맥개럿 소령, 지금까지
겪은 모든 일에 대해
Commander McGarrett, you
have my sincerest apologies
진심을 담아 사과드립니다
for everything
you've been through.
죄송합니다만
사과는 필요 없습니다
All due respect, sir,
I don't need your apologies.
제가 필요한 건
파이브 오 팀을 재창설 해서
What I need you to do
is reinstate
my Five-O task force
이 나쁜 새끼를
잡게 해주는 겁니다
so we can go after
this son of a bitch right here.
파이브 오 팀이 사견해결에
성과를 보였던건 확실 하지요
Well, there is no doubt that
Five-O had an impact on crime,
그러니 부지사 권한으로서
허락 하겠습니다
so as lieutenant governor,
I'll grant your request.
좋아요, 감사합니다
All right. Thank you, sir.
하지만 조건이 있습니다
But there are
conditions.
어떤 조건이요?
What conditions?
제임슨 주지사가
당신들에게 전적인 면책권과
Governor Jameson gave you
full immunity and means
주 법률을 훼손하며
모든 것들을 지원 했죠
to basically
run roughshod
over ever single law
on the state's books.
제 감시 하엔
그런 일은 없을겁니다
That's not going to happen
on my watch.
선을 넘는다면
제게 해명 하십쇼
You cross the line,
you answer to me.
알겠습니다
Understood, sir.
한 가지 집고 넘어가죠
But just so we're clear,
가끔식 생사가
위태로울 때는
sometimes we get put
in positions
where lives are on the line
and we have to make
신속한 결정을
내려야만 하는데
split-second decisions,
and when that happens,
그럴 땐 말씀하신
선 이란게 구분이 힘듭니다
the line you're talking about
gets a little hard to see.
그 정도면 됐어요
Fair enough.
윌리엄스 형사와
캘리 경위는 즉각 복귀하세요
I'll reinstate
Detective Williams
and Lieutenant Kelly
immediately.
칼라코와 경관도
잊지 말아주십쇼
Don't forget
about Officer Kalakaua.
받고 있는 미결 혐의가
모두 벗겨져야 합니다
She needs to be cleared
of all the charges
pending against her as well.
그건 불가능 할 것 같군요
I'm afraid that
won't be possible.
내사과에서 칼라코와 경관을
수사중이라고 들었습니다
I'm told Officer Kalakaua
is still being investigated
by Internal Affairs.
직무적합성을 따지기 위해
수사는 끝 마쳐야 할겁니다
They'll need to complete
that investigation
to determine whether or not
she's fit for duty.
갑시다
Let's go.
있잖아
Hey.
코노는 대체 어디있대?
Where is, uh, Kono anyway?
나도 몰라
I don't know.
한 시간전에
전화 했어야 했는데
She was supposed to check in
an hour ago.
할라와 계곡
넌 못 쏠거야
너 경찰이니까
You won't shoot.
You're a cop.
내 뱃지 본 적 있어?
You see a badge?
- 캘리입니다
- 오빠 지금 당장
Lieutenant Kelly.
Chin, you have to get
코올리나 선착장으로 가
49번 부두야
to Ko'Olina Marina, pier 49.
우 팻이 거기 있어
That's where Wo Fat is.
지금 거래 중이야
The deal's going down now.
거래 끝나면
사라져 버릴거라고
Once it's done,
he's going to disappear.
저 배야
That's it.
너무 늦었어
We're too late.
구매자는 내가 맡을게
I got the buyer.
내가 도우마
너희는 배를 쫓아라
I'll cover her.
You guys go after the boat.
- 나는 조라고 하네
- 코노에요
- I'm Joe.
- Kono.
아주 잘 쐈어
Nice shooting, Kono.
나라면 손 안대겠어
I wouldn't touch that.
국토 안보부에 연락해서
사람들 보내달라 해
Call Homeland Security.
Tell them to get
their people out here.
지저분한 폭탄에 쓰일
원재료를 찾은것 같군
Looks like we got the raw
materials for a dirty bomb.
친, 운전좀 맡아줘
Chin, take the wheel!
가까이 붙여줘
Get us close, okay?
대니, 준비 됐어?
Danny, you ready?
아니
No.
좋아, 가자
Good. Come on.
우 팻은 여기없어
Wo Fat's not here.
멀리가진
못 했을거야
Well, he can't be far away.
우 팻 말이다
어딨냐고
Huh? Wo Fat--
where is he?
어디에 있어?
Where's Wo Fat?
나도 몰라
모른다고
I don't know. I don't know!
봐주지마, 대노
Book him, Danno.
움직여
Come on.
말했잖아
Look, I told you,
난 우 팻이
어딨는지 몰라
I don't know
where Wo Fat is.
네 말 안 믿어
I don't believe you.
이 친구야
뭐가 무서운건데?
Come on. Come on.
What are you scared of?
응?
Hmm?
뭘 것 같아?
What do you think?
나야 모르지
그래서 물어봤잖아
I don't know.
That's why I asked.
하와이 섬으로
돈을 옮기려고 했었어
We were supposed to take
his money to the Big Island,
거기서 보기로 했다고
meet him there.
이게 전부야
That's all I know.
대노 그거 알아?
You know what?
난 믿는다고
I believe you.
나도 이해해
I understand.
그러셔?
Oh, you do?
워, 워
뭐하는 짓이야?
Whoa, whoa.
What are you doing?
너도 들었잖아
You heard the man.
아무것도 모른데
He doesn't know
anything.
가도 돼
이제 자유야
Off you go.
You're free to go.
가
Go.
얼른 가
Go. Go, go, go.
잘했어
이제 쟤는 죽었네
That's good.
He's a... a dead person now.
상어를 잡고 싶으면
밑밥을 뿌려야지
If you want to catch a shark,
you got to chum the waters.
아, 저게 미끼라고?
Oh, that... that's the bait?
쟤가 미끼야
Uh, yeah, he's the bait.
왜 그렇게 봐?
What are you looking
at me like that for?
더 좋은 생각 있어?
You got a better idea?
없잖아
Didn't think so.
파이브 오가 돌아왔군
Five-O back in business.
나만 빼고
For some of us.
너무 불안해 하지마
Hey, you can't sweat this,
cuz, all right?
내 생각엔 몇 주 뒤면
복귀 시킬거야
My guess is you're back on duty
inside a couple of weeks.
그 때 까진 같이 맥주
마시면 안되는 법은 없잖아요
Yeah, and in the
meantime, there's no law
that says you can't grab
a beer with friends, right?
네, 근데
Yeah. I mean...
일 안 하는게
너무 재밌어 졌어요
I mean, I kind of do enjoy
not going to work.
매일 타고 싶은 만큼
서핑도 하고요
Get to surf every day
for as long as I want.
난 25년이나
보드를 안 탔어
I haven't been on a
board in 25 years.
저랑 같이 타러가시죠?
Well, why don't you
come out with me?
남는 보드도 있고
전 자유시간 되게 많아요
I mean, I got the boards
and plenty of free time.
자유시간에
너무 익숙해지진 마
You know what?
Don't get
too used to all that
free time, all right?
비공식적인 고문자리가
필요할지도 모르거든
We may need somebody
in an unofficial
advisory capacity
아니면 여기저기
위장 근무도 있고
or maybe for a little
undercover work here and there.
못 들은걸로 할게
I didn't hear that.
일자리 필요하면
If you're looking for work,
내 새우 트럭에 이쁜
종업원으로 써줄 수 있어
I could use a pretty hostess
at my new shrimp truck.
진짜야?
Really?
난 새우에
알러지 있는데
I'm allergic to shrimp.
그럼 내 새우맛
두부 한 번 먹어봐
You got to try
my shrimp-flavored tofu.
좀 토 나오는데?
Mmm.
That sounds disgusting.
너 방금 짤렸어
You just lost a job.
형
Hey.
고마워
Thank you.
안 고마워도 돼
Don't thank me.
아버지한테
고마워 해
Thank your old man.
아버지 수사가 없었으면
지금 감옥에 있을 수도 있잖아
If it wasn't
for his investigation,
you'd still be in jail
right now.
레이첼 얘기 들었어
Heard about Rachel.
괜찮아 질까?
Is he going
to be okay?
저기
Hey.
혼자 벌써
복직했구나
You're already
behind, partner.
한잔 해
뭐하고 있어?
Drink up.
What are you doing?
CCTV 영상 나머지
살펴보고 있었어
Um, I was going through the rest
of the surveillance footage,
그리고
이걸 찾았거든
and I... I found this.
미팅 같은 건데
This is a meeting
우 팻이랑 주지사..
between Wo Fat
and Governor Jameson...
그리고 네 아버지야
and your old man.
음성은 다 지워졌어
Uh, audio's
all been erased.
영상이 전부야
That's all
we got.
있잖아, 우 팻 말이
맞을 수 도 있어
Maybe... maybe Wo Fat was right.
내 아버지가 부패
했을 수도 있다고
Maybe my father was dirty.
아직 이게 뭔지
잘 모르잖아
Well, we don't know
what this is, okay?
아버지 수사의
일부분 일 수도 있어
This could have been part
of your father's investigation.
잘 되가고 있나?
Everything all right?
아뇨
No.
빅터 헤스한테
물어봐야 됩니다
We need to talk to Victor Hesse.
우 팻이 제 아버지랑
어떠한 거래를 했든
Whatever deal Wo Fat
is making with my father,
그가 뭔가 알고
있을지도 몰라요
he might know
something about it.
나엘남캐 한글자막/싱크수정
수정금지/자유배포